http://www.webserve.ca/privacy-policy

Features
Why Webserve?
Support
Privacy Policy
Statement of Privacy Policy
LAST UPDATED: August 18, 2013
Webserve prides itself on protecting your privacy and developing technology to give you the most powerful and safe online experience possible. This Privacy Policy applies to Webserve and governs data collection and usage. Webserve is governed by the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. By using the Webserve website, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy.
Webserve has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy and security.
How Webserve Collects Your Personal InformationWebserve collects personally identifiable information in a variety of ways. Any information you enter on our websites or online forms for products and services, or that you volunteer in any other way, will be collected. The data collected may include your:
Name
Email address
Home and/or work address and/or telephone number
Credit card and other billing information
Certain information about your computer hardware and software may also be automatically collected by Webserve. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. This information is used by Webserve for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Webserve website and its services.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Webserve public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.
Note: Webserve does not read any of your private online communications.
How Webserve Uses & Discloses Your Personal Information
(i) Provision of Services Webserve collects and uses your personal information to operate the Webserve website and to deliver the services you have requested. Webserve also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Webserve and its affiliates.
(ii) SurveysWebserve may also contact you via surveys to conduct market research and collect opinions about current services or new services that may be offered.
(iii) AnalysisWebserve keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within Webserve in order to determine which Webserve services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Webserve to customers whose behaviour indicates they are interested in a particular subject area.
(iv) Third-Party ServicesWebserve offers some products and services in conjunction with or through trusted partners, sponsors, and affiliates (“Third-Party Services”). If you provide your personal information in conjunction with any Third-Party Services, you will be advised at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy policy applies. If there is any doubt, please contact Webserve to clarify (see contact information below). If this Privacy Policy applies to such personal information, then Webserve may be required to disclose your information to our trusted partner, sponsor, or affiliate in order to provide the Third-Party Services. If the privacy policy of our trusted partner, sponsor, or affiliate applies, Webserve will make all reasonable efforts to ensure the third-party privacy policy is properly in place and complied with. However, it is your responsibility to satisfy yourself with such privacy policies, as Third-Party Services have separate and independent privacy policies. Webserve accepts no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of Third-Party Services. Nonetheless, Webserve welcomes comments and feedback relating to Third-Party Services.
(v) LinksYou may be able to access other websites that have links on Webserve websites, where you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials or new product updates. In many of these cases, you will be asked to provide personal information such as your name, email address, or other contact information, or credit/billing information. If you complete an order or provide personal information to a website or service that is not provided by Webserve, Webserve has no control over the third party’s use of any personal information. Webserve therefore has no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use, disclose, secure, or otherwise deal with your personal information. Webserve provides these links to other websites as a convenience to you. Please exercise care when visiting linked websites, which will have separate and independent privacy policies.
(vi) Legal DisclosureWebserve collects, uses, and discloses your personal information as described above. However, Webserve, its affiliates, trusted partners, and sponsors, may disclose your personal information, including your use of the services or websites accessible through the services, for any reason, in its sole discretion to comply with Canadian, U.S., or other laws, regulations, or governmental or legal requests or demands for such information, and act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Webserve or the public.
Domain RegistrationIn certain jurisdictions or pursuant to the rules of the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers (“ICANN”) or certain registries, domain name registration information legally has to be available to the public. Where domain name registration information is available to the public, anyone can access it through “WHOIS” searches. The WHOIS database is a publicly accessible database that lists the domain name and contact information of the registrant and administrative and technical contacts for the domain name, the name server(s), and the domain name’s creation and expiration date. The domain name registration information you provide may be hosted by us and provided to the public. At times, users of Webserve may receive solicitations that result from searches of the publicly available WHOIS database conducted by other companies or individuals. However, the solicitation and/or SPAM you receive does not in any way come from Webserve and Webserve does not control the use of WHOIS information by third parties. Further, pursuant to ICANN rules, Webserve is required to make WHOIS data available to a third party that enters into a bulk access agreement. ICANN allows individuals to opt-out (using the account management panel, domain management console, or similar service) of their WHOIS information being made available to third parties through bulk access; however, companies, businesses, and other organizations do not have the option to choose not to have their information made available to such a third party under a bulk access agreement. Webserve may also deposit your domain name registration information with a third-party escrow provider to comply with ICANN requirements.
International Transfer of DataIf you visit Webserve or its websites from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with Webserve may result in the transfer of information across international borders. By using Webserve services and communicating with Webserve, you consent to such transfers.
Use of CookiesWebserve uses "cookies" to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Webserve pages, or register with a Webserve site or service, a cookie helps Webserve recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Webserve website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Webserve features that you customized. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Webserve websites or services you visit.
Security of Your Personal InformationWebserve secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Webserve secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Webserve maintains reasonable administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of personal information in its control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed 100% secure. Therefore, while Webserve strives to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond the control of Webserve; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and Webserve through the website cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party, despite best efforts.
Access and Modifying Your InformationYou have the right to access, update, and correct any inaccuracies in your personal information that we control, subject to certain exceptions set out in this Privacy Policy. You may request access, update, and correct any inaccuracies in your personal information by contacting us by email (info@webservesupport.com) or regular mail (Webserve, 115 George St., Suite 511, Oakville, Ontario, Canada L6J 0A2). We may request certain personal information in order to verify your identity.
To ensure you receive the information you need and your privacy is protected, please be sure to regularly update your contact and billing information. You can update all account-related information through the Webserve website.
Changes to this Privacy PolicyWebserve will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. Webserve encourages you to provide feedback and to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of how Webserve is protecting your information.
Sale of BusinessWe wish to clarify and confirm that Webserve may transfer your personal information as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including bankruptcy or insolvency proceedings) involving all or part of Webserve, whether by corporate reorganization, share sale, asset sale, or other change of control. Webserve may share your personal information with other entities owned by Webserve or that own Webserve.
Contact InformationWebserve welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that Webserve has not adhered to this Privacy Policy or you require any changes or access to your personal information, please contact us at info@webservesupport.com.
Alternatively, you can contact us in writing at:
Webserve 115 George St., Suite 511 Oakville, Ontario L6J 0A2
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
